https://www.ghorthodontics.com/privacy-policy?hsLang=en

Updated: May 25, 2018
Your privacy is important to us.
This Online Privacy Policy explains how G&H Orthodontics and its affiliates ("G&H Orthodontics," "we," "us," and "our") protect your privacy when you visit this website. This policy applies to "Personal Information", information that identifies you personally, either alone or in combination with other information available to us.
Please take a few minutes to review this Online Privacy Policy. By accessing or using this Site, you are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information as set forth in this Online Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this privacy policy, please exit and do not use this website.
This Online Privacy Policy describes what types of information we gather and track when you use our websites, how this information is used and with whom it is shared. If you have any questions about this Online Privacy Policy, please contact us.
This Online Privacy Policy includes the following:
What Information We CollectHow We May Use and Share Your InformationLocation of InformationChildren’s PrivacySecurityChanges to This Online Privacy PolicyYour ChoicesContact G&H Orthodontics
What Information We Collect
When you visit our website, we may collect anonymous or personally identifiable information from you. Personally identifiable information is information that can identify you, such as your full name, email address, postal address, telephone number, and fax number. In some cases, you may provide information to us, and in other cases information about you or your activities on our Services may be automatically collected.
If permitted by applicable law, we may collect the following information:
Information You Provide. We collect the personal information you knowingly provide by completing an online form, registering for information or services, applying for a job, or otherwise sending to us.
Supplemental Information. From time to time, we may supplement the information you give us with information from other sources, such as information validating your address, information based on your zip code or business, or information that we have based upon your relationship with G&H Orthodontics. For example, if you are a G&H Orthodontics customer or supplier, we may supplement the information you provide online with information you provide through your business relationship with G&H Orthodontics.
Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser. We collect information that is sent to us automatically by your web browser. This information typically includes your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the identity of your internet service provider, the name and version of your operating system and browser, the date and time of your visit, the page that linked you to G&H Orthodontics, and the pages you visit.
Cookies and Other Technologies. G&H Orthodontics may use "cookie" technology on this website. A cookie contains information that is sent by a website and stored in your hard drive or temporary memory. You may change your cookie settings on your internet browser or delete our cookies at any time. We may use cookies to save your preferences for our websites or to collect statistics related to the number of visitors to our websites and requests for files, the types of browsers used, and other aggregate data. This website uses Google Analytics to help analyze how visitors use this site. Google Analytics utilizes the data it collects to track and examine the use of our website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. For more information about how we use cookies read our Cookie Policy, and see our Manage Your Cookie Settings page to manage your cookie preferences.
How We May Use and Share Your Personal Information
If permitted by applicable law, we may use the personal information we collect through our website:
to provide products, information and services you request;
to provide you with effective customer service;
to improve the content, functionality, performance and usability of our website;
to improve our marketing and promotional efforts;
to provide technical support and troubleshooting; and
for security, credit or fraud prevention purposes;
to send periodic e–mails;
to process your orders or requests;
for any other purpose identified in an applicable privacy statement or other agreement you have with G&H Orthodontics.
If permitted by applicable law, we may share your information as described below:
Within G&H Orthodontics. We may share your personal information with G&H Orthodontics affiliates for the purposes set forth in this Online Privacy Policy.
Our Service Providers. We may share your personal information with companies or organizations, including subsidiaries, affiliates, and other entities that perform services on our behalf, such as website support service providers. In each case, such third parties are required to use adequate privacy protections and may use the information only for the purpose of providing services to G&H Orthodontics.
Business Transactions and Transfers. G&H Orthodontics may buy, sell, form, or otherwise reorganize one or more of its businesses or sell stock or assets, for example, as the result of a sale, merger, reorganization or liquidation. A transaction of this type may involve the disclosure of your information to prospective purchasers or partners who have signed a confidentiality agreement with G&H Orthodontics.
Compliance with Laws and Protection of Our Rights and the Rights of Others. We may disclose personal information when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law, a court order or a subpoena. We may also disclose personal information to cooperate with a government investigation; to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce or apply this Online Privacy Policy or our other agreements; or to protect our own rights or property or the rights, property or safety of our users or others.
We may process your personal information for our legitimate business interests, these include but are not limited to: fraud prevention, direct marketing, network and information systems security, data analytics or data enhancement, modifying or improving our services, identifying usage trends, and determining the effectiveness of promotional campaigns and advertising. You have the right to object to this processing.
We will not use your personal information to send product or promotional advertising unless you have agreed to receive product or promotional advertising. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails from us, we include an unsubscribe button at the bottom of each email. Other than the purposes described above, G&H Orthodontics does not provide or sell your personal information to third-parties.
Location of Information
G&H Orthodontics is a global organization with its corporate headquarters in the United States. Our servers, databases, and service providers are located in the United States and in other countries. Different countries have different privacy laws and requirements, and some, including the United States, may provide less legal protection for your personal information than others. By using this site, you are consenting to the collection, use and transfer of your personal information in or to the United States or other countries for the purposes described in this Online Privacy Policy.
Children’s Privacy
We do not knowingly collect information from children to sell or promote our products or services. We do not invite minors to contact us or provide personal information. Visitors must be 18 years of age or older to submit registration or survey information. If you believe a child under the age of eighteen has sent personal contact information to G&H Orthodontics, please contact us immediately at the address listed below, and we will use reasonable efforts to promptly remove that information from our databases.
Security
We take commercially reasonable precautions to protect the confidentiality, integrity and security of your personal information. We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via SSL (Secure Sockets Layers) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
We urge users to be careful with personal information while using the Internet. "Perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, and we cannot guarantee the safety of transmitting personal information over the Internet.
Changes to This Online Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to modify this Online Privacy Policy and related business practices at any time by posting updated text on this site and updated effective date at the bottom of this page. As we add new features and functionality to our websites or G&H Orthodontics policies or applicable laws evolve, we may need to update or revise this Online Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to do so, at any time and without prior notice, by posting a revised version on our website. These changes will be effective as of the date we post a revised version on our website. Your use of one of our websites following any such change constitutes your consent to the terms of the revised Online Privacy Policy. For this reason, it is important for you to review this Online Privacy Policy regularly.
Your Choices
We respect your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use and disclose your personal information. In some cases, we will ask you to indicate your choices at the time we collect your personal information. If you receive email or marketing communications, you may "opt–out" of receiving e-mail and other communications from us at any time by using the unsubscribe feature included in the e–mails we send. If you are a customer of G&H Orthodontics products, we reserve the right to contact you with information regarding health and safety, applicable regulations, or stewardship of our product.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Updating and Accessing Personal Information
Under the law of some countries, you may have the right to access the information G&H Orthodontics holds about you, correct mistakes in that information, and to delete personal information. If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or request deletion on our site by submitting your request via this page to our customer service team. We will respond to requests within 30 days. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
Contact G&H Orthodontics
If you have any questions about this Online Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us via phone at the numbers listed in the Contact Us section of our website. You may also send postal correspondence to:
G&H Orthodontics2165 Earlywood DriveFranklin, Indiana 46131USA
If you have concerns that someone affiliated with G&H Orthodontics has used your information in a manner that is not consistent with this Online Privacy Policy; would like to seek guidance related to G&H Orthodontics’s Code of Business Conduct; or report potential unethical business practices or other violations of our Code of Business Conduct, please contact G&H Orthodontics in either of the ways listed above.
To the top
PRODUCTS
Brackets
Bands
Buccal Tubes
Wires
Elastomerics
View Catalog
Mailing Address2165 Earlywood DriveFranklin, IN 46131 USA
Phone1-800-526-1026 (US & Canada)1-317-346-6655 (International)
Privacy Policy | Cookie Policy | Terms and Conditions
G&H, OrthoForce, OrthoClub, ODP and the G&H logo are registered trademarks of G&H Wire Company. All other trademarks are property of their respective owner.
© 2020 G&H® Orthodontics. All rights reserved.
